The sun's setting? Already?
It can't be. Guys!
He really was telling the truth!
The priest's new ability!
He already had it back on the shuttle!
And now everything is
moving at a faster speed!
Everything in this world is...
And I don't just mean the machines.
I'm talking literally everything.
Oh shit, the sun's already gone down.
Does that mean the
completion of his ability?
Where is he?
Where did that bastard go?
The longest I can stop time
is five seconds at most.
I have to locate him and strike him down.
All in the span of five seconds.
That's the limit.
Now time will resume.
What?
It can't be!
He's using it as a spring!
I will make this clear once and for all.
Time will keep racing by.
But for your clarification?
I did not obtain this ability just
so I could dispose of you all!
nor did I do it to
become the most powerful.
The true purpose of this ability
is to guide the masses of humanity.
towards everlasting happiness.
Allow me to introduce you to my
new stand, my gift to humanity.
I shall christen my stand...
Made in Heaven!
Itaami wo nori Cairo tabi
Kokoro wa eilu
ni togisuma sareru
Cairo kai Zero Chaka
mei no sai hate de
I'll
see
you
next time.
The reason for my disposing of you
all is for the future of humanity.
Your deaths here are nothing personal.
For the sake of all mankind's happiness,
you shall become necessary sacrifices.
Ghost gun! Fire!
It's no use, Emporio!
Bullets aren't gonna hit him!
Nuh-uh, Jolene!
I aim for the wall of
the next building over!
And I must put one of her
stickers on the bullet!
Thanks to that, there are two bullets now!
Emporio...
He's coming back around!
Hold on tightly, everyone!
No matter what happens, we
can't let go of each other!
Crap, it's him!
He's chasing us!
Because smack is a stand, its
movements aren't accelerated!
But he's on our asses!
Emporio!
Put a sticker on another one of
your bullets and shoot again!
We're gonna make our way to
the wetlands just like this!
Head towards the ocean!
If we're surrounded by water, there's one
way we can kill this psycho time wizard!
The priest already caught up to us!
He's gonna wait for us at that building!
Use this next bullet to change
our trajectory, Emporio!
To the ocean!
That's where we need to be!
Focus on the marshes and aim the bullet
at the rocks jutting out of the water!
He's coming this way!
He's too fast! Listen,
even if the priest is able to pursue us
through this state of accelerated time,
he only has one stand.
Also, I'm willing to bet that
its power is only above average.
He has no other choice but to pick
each of us off, one at a time.
That's when we have the
chance to beat him down.
At the exact moment when he tries
to come in and end my life, Mr.
Jotaro, that's when I'm
going to give you a signal.
When I do, stop time immediately and
kill that fucker before he gets away.
As for the timing,
you're going to want to
stop time at precisely
the same instant that
his attack hits my body.
Do you hear me?
Don't stop it any earlier than that.
Do it after.
This is all going to happen quickly.
The timing is important.
You'll have to grab him
while he's in mid-attack.
And to do that, your
Star Platinum is the key.
Yo, wait a second.
You're doing what?
I don't understand.
What are you trying to say?
Anastasia, that's a good idea.
But although Poochie said he'll end you
first, he might not act on his words.
We can't trust what he says.
Thinking about it a bit more
logically, you'll end me first. No.
I get why you might think
that, but it isn't accurate.
My Diver Drive is already in your
body, protecting you like before.
And it's not just you.
Jolene, Emporio, and Ermes too.
You're all safe.
As long as you stay within
an arm's length of me.
So no matter who ends up
getting attacked first,
the brunt of that first blow will
be absorbed by my Diver Drive.
After that you'll feel
a sensation through your
body that's gonna be the
signal from my stand!
That it's go time we
clear that's how it has to
be time can't stop until
after his attack lands!
Anastasia are you going for a draw?
What no way are you out of your mind?
His next attack will definitely
kill you most likely but maybe
before he strikes my vitals I can
manage to send the signal off!
I have been having good luck
recently haven't I Emporio?
Since I broke out of prison
I've managed not to die somehow!
If I can just keep on
living when this shitstorm
is over I'm finally gonna
ask Jolene to marry me
or something like that! You know?
Sure!
Go ahead.
Just propose.
I'm not saying this because I'm
in despair over our situation.
There's still some hope left in your plan.
It's not dark at all.
There might be only one path, but
if there's even a sliver of hope,
then that'll be the path to success.
He's over there!
He's already on the rock
ahead of us! Emporio!
Everybody, gather up!
Get closer to me, now!
There!
He's coming around to the right!
He's here!
I see.
Due to the splashes,
being surrounded by water makes it
easier to see which way he's going.
Not yet, Mr. Jotaro.
Whatever you do, don't stop time yet.
If he gets away, it's all over.
Capturing him is the
only way we can win this.
You've got to sense the
signal with your body.
Hey, wait a second. Look up.
What's wrong with all the clouds?
They're racing by at insane
speeds like a rocket.
and what the heck is going on?
The sky to the east is getting brighter.
What the hell?
Seriously, aren't they
moving way too fast?
An hour was supposed to feel
like two to three minutes,
which means it should have
taken at least 20 to 30 minutes?
for the sun to rise again.
It doesn't make sense.
The sun is coming up at
an impossibly high speed.
Hey, what the hell does that mean?
Isn't that time is starting
to accelerate even more now?
Birds all over the world are still
flying at their natural speed.
So are butterflies and other insects.
Also,
there are no reported
cases of flowers or plants
blooming abruptly or
withering away at rapid rates.
See this glass?
I'm currently holding it in my hand.
As long as it remains in my grasp, nothing
happens even if I shake or swirl it.
However, once I remove
my grip from the glass...
You see?
We can't even see it fall.
It's already broken on the
floor before you realize.
It the only possible explanation for this
phenomenon is that time
is Accelerating everything
in the world is
progressively getting faster
except for The movements
of living organisms.
This is all my assistance fault.
I'm the Number one monthly manga artist.
Yeah there's no way that I could have
only Drawn one page in the entire night.
It's not possible.
Oh, what?
And for some reason, the ink on the pen
dries before it even touches the paper.
What am I supposed to do?
Yes, what is it? What?
There's a manga artist
that's still got it in?
And who could that be?
What kind of person are they?
Rohan Kishibe.
The tide's going too fast.
I can't see the movement of the waves.
We can't read where the
priest is going like this.
Shit!
Where is he going to come from?
Everyone get ready!
Stone Ocean!
Smack!
Mr.
Jotaro, not just yet.
We're almost there.
Wait for the signal to come.
Do it now! Stop time!
Stop platinum! The world!
I got you!
Take this, Father Pochi!
What?!
He used Jolene's stand
to attack Anastasia!
He's a step ahead of us!
Only four more seconds.
If I'm not able to finish him off now,
I'll just hide within the
accelerating time again.
As soon as time resumes,
we'll be done for!
I have to go at him with everything
I've got while I still can!
Three more seconds!
Two seconds!
Knives!
While he was falling, the priest had
already thrown them into the air,
just like how Dio did in the past.
Oh my, it seems you
were late by two steps.
The Joestar bloodline has to be expected.
They drew strength from
their pride and courage,
and came together to conquer their fate.
However, that connection through
blood is also their weakness.
Jotaro Kujo, your greatest
weakness is your daughter.
Push - push - push - Push -
push
- Hey,
old man.
Don't leave.
I did steal a car.
I was leaving school.
In the supermarket parking
lot, there was a car.
Why did I do something like that?
But I know Dad's gonna come save me.
He'll be here.
Definitely.
Dad'll be here soon.
To save me.
I must eliminate any obstacles
in the way of my destiny.
I feel no remorse for them or
you, nor will I let you go free.
I'll put an end to everything.
But to you, young Emporio, I'm the
one who killed your mother, aren't I?
Shoot me then, pull the trigger so you can
leave this godforsaken world as a martyr.
This is where your fate comes to an end!
Emporia!
Jolene Kujo!
Showstar!
Do you truly think you can get away?
The speed at which you swim through water
is slower than if you
were running on land!
Jolene!
I caught a dolphin with Stone Ocean.
No matter how fast time is going,
every living creature is
moving at its natural speed.
And then there's you, Father Poochy.
With your speed, you could probably
catch up to this dolphin easily.
But distance is what matters.
You can reach us at close range.
But how many meters can
you keep on swimming for?
500 meters?
Maybe even 800?
A hundred?
How long can you last?
Can you swim longer distances than
a dolphin without getting tired?
That has nothing to do
with the flow of time.
It's still the same distance whether
you're picking something up or swimming.
That doesn't change. And plus,
it has to be at a distance where you
can swim back to shore without drowning.
I won't ever let you get away.
This tiresome feud between us ends now.
I can't have any trace of
your existence in my future.
Chulene, climb the rope.
Hurry up and come to the dolphin!
Emporio, because of Anastasia's
sacrificing himself to protect my father,
I'm still alive, but
that's the only reason.
And thanks to Ermes buying
time attacking the priest,
I was able to extend my
rope to catch this dolphin.
When dolphins let people
ride on their back,
I heard that they swim in a way
that their rider won't ever drown.
Hurry! Hurry!
Get over here already, Jolene!
Your rope is unraveling even more!
I know without a doubt
that Dolphin is going
to carry you somewhere
safe and out of danger.
What are you saying? Hurry!
You can still make it over to me!
Emporium, I can't go with you.
Wherever I go, the Priest will sense the
presence of the Joestar blood within me.
And no matter how far I
run, I'll sense him too.
He'll keep following me forever.
If I stay here, you won't
be able to get away.
Everything will be okay, Emporio.
You'll be going the rest
of the way yourself.
You can do this.
I have total faith in your capabilities.
The ones who died so that you could
live are Anastasia, our friend Ermes,
and my father,
Jotaro Keicho.
Keep on living.
Your only hope!
I don't know what the heck
you're even talking about!
No! Please don't go!
Just wait! Hold on! Jolyne!
Stop! Don't leave me!
Hurry and pull yourself
off the rope already!
He's getting worn out.
I'll hold him off for as long as I can!
Bring it, Father Poochie!
Stone Ocean!
No!
July!
Whoa, hey, what's that?
Is that the sun rising? No way!
The sun's coming up again already?
It doesn't even look
like a sphere anymore!
It's more like a long belt of light!
The hands on my watch disappeared! No!
They're just going way too fast
for me to see with the naked eye!
The day's over! It's over!
Now it's morning!
And night again!
This is crazy!
Time is accelerating even more!
Shit!
This is really bad!
Get the canned food!
All the raw meat's gonna rot
and we can't eat it anymore!
Buy it out!
Buy out all the canned food!
We're gonna run out of food!
Look at all this window dust collecting!
The frame is rotting!
Whoa, my teeth!
The implants I just got
put in are falling out!
What the hell, man?
What's with the sky?
Where the fuck did the sun go?
Is that strip of light in the
sky supposed to be the sun?
Is the time noon or is it night?
What day of the week is it?
And for that matter, what's even the year?
It's starting to get really cold.
The climate is changing, too.
What's going on?
The rocks are changing
shape because of the waves.
Is time ever going to stop speeding up?
How much more?
How much longer is this
nightmare going to last?
Now even the terrain is changing too!
What in the world is this? How bizarre!
It's only living things!
I can't breathe!
What in God's name are you doing
in here without any clothes on?
Huh?
What the... I...
Shut up and stop stalling!
You and the prisoners need to get dressed!
But why am I naked too, though?
I mean, what happened?
Time was going all fast, and then...
This ain't good!
I'm naked on camera!
They'll misunderstand!
Is this...
This place is...
I've been here!
I know it!
This place is Green Dolphin
Street State Prison.
And I'm in the hallway in
front of the visiting room.
Although you think I cope!
My head is filled with hope.
Of some place
other than here.
Although you think I smile!
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.